apcmedia.com 2000-10-18

# APC - Online Privacy Policy

   The APC Online Privacy Policy provides information regarding accuracy, access, security and how APC controls client information acquired from its Website(s).

The _APC Website_ mission

   The mission of the _APC Website_ is to provide clients with the most up-to-date product and company information and present it in a manner best suited to their needs. The _APC Website_ may be accessed by all Internet users on a 24/7 basis.

   The _APC Website_ is the most accurate source of information on APC and its products/services. Questions regarding the accuracy of information on the _APC Website_ may be directed to the webmaster.

Handling of personal information

   APC requests information from clients if they choose to subscribe to email lists, place orders or if they choose to respond to advertising, promotions, sweepstakes or contests. This personal information is necessary in order for APC to fulfill the client's request.

   This information may also be used by APC to contact or update the client with periodic APC publications, product details or other special offers. APC does allow other reputable companies to offer special services or products of value to the client. The client may unsubscribe at any time by directing their request to [apccurrents@apcc.com](mailto:apccurrents@apcc.com). In the case of email, only clients who have consented to receive E-mail updates are included on E-mail lists and instructions on how to "unsubscribe" from further solicitations is included in every such email they receive from APC. 

    _APC Website_ management uses IP addresses to diagnose Webserver problems and to administrate the _APC Website_. Cookies may be used to store client variables such as keeping track of the inventory of an online shopping cart, limiting repeated exposure to the same ads or bypassing login prompts by "remembering" passwords across sessions.

APC E-Commerce Website(s)

   The collection of personal information and similar transactions performed by the APC E-Commerce Website(s) are secured via SSL encryption. This information is used to process orders. Concerns regarding E-Commerce may be directed to [commercemaster@apcc.com](mailto:commercemaster@apcc.com). 

APC is not interested in minors

   APC has no desire to collect information from those under the age of 18. In an instance where such information were collected it would be purely accidental and unintentional. APC encourages parents to discuss the Internet with their children and monitor personal information that a child may provide via the Internet.
